mosaic-service.com 2009-09-05

# Privacy Policy

**Mosaic is committed towards maintaining privacy of its customers.**

This is the web site of Mosaic ITES Services Pvt. Ltd. 

**Our postal address is**  
A-14, Sector-7, Noida,  
Uttar Pradesh, 201301 

We can be reached via e-mail at [sales@mosaic-service.com ](mailto:sales@mosaic-service.com)or you can reach us by telephone at (0120) 4626500 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address. 

**Mosaic ITES Services Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is our prime concern. The policy explains all our online information practices and enables you to make informed choices. The policy is easily accessible and is linked to each page on the website through the Footer . 

## Information Collected 

This policy is valid for all information collected throughout the [Mosaic ITES Services] website. The website has number of pages requiring different information from the customers. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information only if there is a purchase online. 

## How your information is used 

We never use/share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order. Return email addresses are used to answer the email we receive and to give timely notification of our project, or service news and updates. Email addresses are also used to provide a free subscription to our Newsletter. These addresses are never shared with any outside individual or Company. ****

As per Mosaic's policy, we never use or share any personally identifiable information provided to us online except the ways described above. Also an opportunity to opt out or prohibit such uses is also given. 

## We are committed to data security 

Appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures are in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. This prevents any form of unauthorized access, and helps maintain data accuracy, and also ensures the correct use of information. 

## Cookies 

We do not set any cookies. 

## Correct your information 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us an e-mail request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Policy changes 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. 

## Contact Us 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated Privacy policy, you may contact us at (0120) 4626500 or send an email to [sales@mosaic-service.com ](mailto:sales@mosaic-service.com).
